https://www.mhe-usa.com/privacy-policy

Call Toll Free 800-861-4643
E-mail us at mhe@mhe-usa.com
HomeOur CompanyProductsBelow-the-Hook LiftersConveyor SystemsCustom ProductsFall ProtectionHydraulic & Air ManipulatorsHydraulic TiltersLift TablesModular Office & EnclosuresRack Storage SystemsWorkstation Cranes & HoistsManufacturersLatest NewsContact
Site Menu
Site Menu
HomeOur CompanyProductsBelow-the-Hook LiftersConveyor SystemsCustom ProductsFall ProtectionHydraulic & Air ManipulatorsHydraulic TiltersLift TablesModular Office & EnclosuresRack Storage SystemsWorkstation Cranes & HoistsManufacturersLatest NewsContact
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy tells you what PII we may collect from you, how we may share your PII, and how you can limit our sharing of your PII. Materials Handling Enterprises is committed to the security and privacy of all our clients.
Materials Handling Enterprises respects your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of your PII you share with us.
Links to Other Websites
Our Website may contain links to other websites. You must understand that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy. These websites will likely have their own privacy policies. We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience.
You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies of these websites to see how they treat your personal information.
Information We Collect
Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website. As a visitor to our Website, you can browse our Website to find out more about us. You are not required to provide us with any PII as a Visitor.
Online Forms
There may be online forms used on our Website. The information you enter into these online forms may contain PII.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If our company decides to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our website so our users are always aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. Your continued use of our website after any change to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Featured Products
Storage Racks, Stacking Frames, and Rack Accessories
Rack storage systems we offer include pallet racking systems, storage racks, and more.
Learn More »
Below the Hook Lifting Devices and Lifting Equipment
Grip, lift and transport your products with our below the hook lifting devices.
Learn More »
Request a Quote
Your E-mail Address:
Your Name: *
E-mail Address: *
Comments or Questions: *
View Catalog »
,
,
2020 © Materials Handling Enterprises, Inc.
Powered by Epic Web Studios
